<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sai Praneeth on Sai Praneeth</title>
    <link>https://spmuppar.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sai Praneeth on Sai Praneeth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Mesh refinement based Tabulated equation of state</title>
      <link>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/adaptive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 06:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/adaptive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Non-ideal state equations are needed to compute a growing number of engineering-relevant problems. The additional computational overhead from the complex thermodynamics accounts for a significant portion of the total computation, especially the near-critical or transcritical thermodynamic regimes. A compromise between computational speed and the accuracy of the thermodynamic property evaluations results in a propagation of the error from the thermodynamics to the hydrodynamic computations.  This work proposes a systematic error quantification and computational cost estimate of the various approaches for equation of state computation for use in compressible Navier-Stokes solvers in the supercritical regime. We develop a parallelized, high-order, finite volume solver with highly-modular thermodynamic implementation to compute the compressible equations in conservative form. Three tabular approaches are investigated: homogeneous tabulation, block structured adaptive mesh refinement tabulation, and a n-dimensional Bezier surface patch on an adaptive structured mesh. We define a set of  standardized error metrics and evaluate the thermodynamic error, table size and computational expense for each approach. We also present an uncertainty quantification methodology for tabular equation of state.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Portfolio Management and Statistical Analysis of S&amp;P 500 traded securities</title>
      <link>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/fin_port/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 06:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/fin_port/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The computation of daily returns and descriptive statistics of 3 US car stocks(F, GM, TSLA) over a 5 year period using Modern Portfolio Theory (MPT) to formulate efficient portfolios from individual assets and compute portfolio frontier. I implemented Random Walk (RW) and ARIMA time series model to simulate time history of stock price for forecasting&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-class Classification Algorithms for Hand Written Digits</title>
      <link>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/digit_class/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 06:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/digit_class/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of Santander Bank&#39;s customer spending behaviour</title>
      <link>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/ml_santander/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 06:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/ml_santander/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty quantification of tabulated supercritical thermodynamics for compressible Navier-Stokes solvers</title>
      <link>https://spmuppar.github.io/publication/tabulated-supercritical-thermo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 01:20:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spmuppar.github.io/publication/tabulated-supercritical-thermo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poster: Tabulated supercritical thermodynamics for compressible Navier-Stokes solvers</title>
      <link>https://spmuppar.github.io/publication/poster_tab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 06:00:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spmuppar.github.io/publication/poster_tab/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real fluid effects on Shock Tube flow at supercritical conditions</title>
      <link>https://spmuppar.github.io/publication/real_gas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 06:12:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spmuppar.github.io/publication/real_gas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFD modelling of heat transfer in Geothermal heat exchanger</title>
      <link>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/cfd_hx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/cfd_hx/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real fluid effects on Shock Tube flow at supercritical conditions</title>
      <link>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/real_fluid_shock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spmuppar.github.io/project/real_fluid_shock/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A study on shock tube simulations under supercritical thermodynamic conditions to investigate real fluid effects on the wave propagation. The numerical methods are an approximate riemann solver modified for real fluid thermodynamics. Three cases are studied supercriticial, nearcritical and subcritical conditions. Also an attempt has been made to study the transcritical case using the double flux method, but the spurious pressure oscillations failed the simulation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
