<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SAI PRANEETH on SAI PRANEETH</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SAI PRANEETH on SAI PRANEETH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>I am taking #100DaysofMLCode challenge</title>
      <link>/post/100daysmlcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/100daysmlcode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/llSourcell/100_Days_of_ML_Code&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;#100DaysofMLCode&lt;/a&gt; challenge involves coding and/or studying machine learning for atleast an hour everyday for the next 100 days. I am pledging today that I will be taking this challenge starting today and I will post my daily updates as a log in both &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/spmuppar&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;github&lt;/a&gt; and here in my website as a blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the today update,
I&amp;rsquo;m currently in my Week 3 Programming assignment for Coursera&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.coursera.org/learn/convolutional-neural-networks&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Convolutional Neural Networks course&lt;/a&gt; (part of Deep learning specialization). This assignment is about &amp;ldquo;Autonomous driving - Car detection&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will be learning about object detection using the very powerful YOLO model. Many of the ideas in this notebook are described two papers:  &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1506.02640&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Redmon et al., 2016&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1612.08242&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Redmon and Farhadi, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective is to learn,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using object detection on a car detection dataset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to deal with bounding boxes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem Statement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are working on an autonomous self-driving car, the most critical part of this project is to build a car detection system. To collect data, a mounted camera on the hood, which takes pictures for every few seconds while you drive. The dataset that was used in this assignment was obtained by &lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.ai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;drive.ai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;YOLO
2.1 Model details
2.2 Filtering with a threshold on class scores
2.3 Non-max suppression&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.4 Wrapping up the filtering&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;
  
  
  
  
    
      
    
  
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-1&#34; data-caption=&#34;Image credit: [**Correlation-one**](https://www.correlation-one.com/)&#34; href=&#34;/img/proba_map.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;/img/proba_map.png&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appeared on BNN Bloomberg for the first time</title>
      <link>/post/bnn_bloomberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bnn_bloomberg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two weeks ago the Citadel&amp;rsquo;s Data Open competition was covered by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;BNN Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt; and our winning team was featured shortly in their story. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/video/wall-street-puts-out-all-stops-to-woo-canadian-tech-talent-away-from-silicon-valley~1399866&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wall Street puts out all stops to woo Canadian tech talent away from Silicon Valley&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the &lt;a href=&#34;https://webapps.9c9media.com/vidi-player/1.4.3/share/iframe.html?currentId=1399866&amp;amp;config=bnn/share.json&amp;amp;kruxId=InSaVlLc&amp;amp;cid=%5B%7B%22contentId%22%3A1399866%2C%22ad%22%3A%7B%22adsite%22%3A%22ctv.bnn%22%2C%22adzone%22%3A%22ctv.bnn%22%7D%7D%5D&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;
  
  
  
  
    
      
    
  
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-1&#34; data-caption=&#34;Image credit: [**Correlation-one**](https://www.correlation-one.com/)&#34; href=&#34;/img/bnn_bl.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;/img/bnn_bl.png&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
  
  
  
    
      
    
  
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-1&#34; data-caption=&#34;Image credit: [**Correlation-one**](https://www.correlation-one.com/)&#34; href=&#34;/img/bnn_bl3.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;/img/bnn_bl3.png&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converting Credit to Cash; the art of Stoozing</title>
      <link>/post/credit_to_cash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/credit_to_cash/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;All of us own credit cards and some of us are capable of getting sound credit in the order of 20-30,000$ Which is interest free, it came to my mind that what if we &lt;strong&gt;invest&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;buy&lt;/strong&gt; some form of riskless or guaranteed instrument for the grace period. ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously the process is not that simple, going to a nearby ATM and withdrawing from your credit card would be the craziest thing that you can do, as it attracts ~20% interest &lt;strong&gt;from that moment&lt;/strong&gt; and turns out to be very costly. But you&amp;rsquo;re entitled to buy anything from the same credit card like goods, services, commodities and so on. There are few websites that allow you to buy forex, cryptocurrencies using credit cards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what&amp;rsquo;s the catch here ? What if I use my credit card to buy $20k worth of cryptocurrency and reconvert it into cash ? Hmm, it is certainly possible but you&amp;rsquo;ll lose something in the process of doing so, in the name of transaction charges. Most of the cryptocurrency exchanges charge 6-10% commission on the credit card transactions. So, there goes our plan A.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Mesh refinement based Tabulated equation of state</title>
      <link>/project/adaptive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 06:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/adaptive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Non-ideal state equations are needed to compute a growing number of engineering-relevant problems. The additional computational overhead from the complex thermodynamics accounts for a significant portion of the total computation, especially the near-critical or transcritical thermodynamic regimes. A compromise between computational speed and the accuracy of the thermodynamic property evaluations results in a propagation of the error from the thermodynamics to the hydrodynamic computations.  This work proposes a systematic error quantification and computational cost estimate of the various approaches for equation of state computation for use in compressible Navier-Stokes solvers in the supercritical regime. We develop a parallelized, high-order, finite volume solver with highly-modular thermodynamic implementation to compute the compressible equations in conservative form. Three tabular approaches are investigated: homogeneous tabulation, block structured adaptive mesh refinement tabulation, and a n-dimensional Bezier surface patch on an adaptive structured mesh. We define a set of  standardized error metrics and evaluate the thermodynamic error, table size and computational expense for each approach. We also present an uncertainty quantification methodology for tabular equation of state.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Portfolio Management and Statistical Analysis of S&amp;P 500 traded securities</title>
      <link>/project/fin_port/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 06:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/fin_port/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The computation of daily returns and descriptive statistics of 3 US car stocks(F, GM, TSLA) over a 5 year period using Modern Portfolio Theory (MPT) to formulate efficient portfolios from individual assets and compute portfolio frontier. I implemented Random Walk (RW) and ARIMA time series model to simulate time history of stock price for forecasting&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving 311 service through GeoSpatial Analysis and Time series Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/data_open/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 06:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/data_open/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New York city’s 311 non emergency call system sees an incredible amount of traffic every year. In 2017, the number of 311 contacts set its 4th consecutive annual record with nearly 40 million requests, surpassing 2016 by 11% (nyc.gov). With such a large volume of traffic, it is important for the government to be able to not only address requests efficiently, but allocate appropriate resources as well. With this in mind, we pose the following topic question in analyzing the dataset:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Topic Question:&lt;/strong&gt; What suggestions can we make to improve the resolution efficiency of 311 service
requests in New York?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Improved government services can do a lot for improving the daily life of New Yorkers. In this report we show that the structure of the 311 service complaints/ requests is a criterion develop a unique profile of the local city, thereby serving as an efficient and low-cost decision system for relevant city stakeholders. We will be analyzing two factors in particular to assist 311 service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How can we accommodate the needs of people from different zip codes?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can we use time series analysis to make predictions on call volume?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By answering these questions, we hope that 311-services can optimize their services to improve the health and welfare of NYC residents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Github repo: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/spmuppar/The-Data-Open-Citadel&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://github.com/spmuppar/The-Data-Open-Citadel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-class Classification Algorithms for Hand Written Digits</title>
      <link>/project/digit_class/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 06:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/digit_class/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pairs Trading with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/project/pairs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 06:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/pairs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[still working]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of Santander Bank&#39;s customer spending behaviour</title>
      <link>/project/ml_santander/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 06:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/ml_santander/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty quantification of tabulated supercritical thermodynamics for compressible Navier-Stokes solvers</title>
      <link>/publication/tabulated-supercritical-thermo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 01:20:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/tabulated-supercritical-thermo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poster: Tabulated supercritical thermodynamics for compressible Navier-Stokes solvers</title>
      <link>/publication/poster_tab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 06:00:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/poster_tab/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real fluid effects on Shock Tube flow at supercritical conditions</title>
      <link>/publication/real_gas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 06:12:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/real_gas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Talk</title>
      <link>/talk/example-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/example-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Embed your slides or video here using &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/post/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;. Further details can easily be added using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFD modelling of heat transfer in Geothermal heat exchanger</title>
      <link>/project/cfd_hx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cfd_hx/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real fluid effects on Shock Tube flow at supercritical conditions</title>
      <link>/project/real_fluid_shock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/real_fluid_shock/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A study on shock tube simulations under supercritical thermodynamic conditions to investigate real fluid effects on the wave propagation. The numerical methods are an approximate riemann solver modified for real fluid thermodynamics. Three cases are studied supercriticial, nearcritical and subcritical conditions. Also an attempt has been made to study the transcritical case using the double flux method, but the spurious pressure oscillations failed the simulation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
