<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on SAI PRANEETH</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on SAI PRANEETH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Appeared on BNN Bloomberg for the first time</title>
      <link>/post/bnn_bloomberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bnn_bloomberg/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago the Citadel&amp;rsquo;s Data Open competition was covered by BNN Bloomberg and our winning team was featured shortly in their story. Wall Street puts out all stops to woo Canadian tech talent away from Silicon Valley
Here is the video
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converting Credit to Cash; the art of Stoozing</title>
      <link>/post/credit_to_cash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/credit_to_cash/</guid>
      <description>All of us own credit cards and some of us are capable of getting sound credit in the order of 20-30,000$ Which is interest free, it came to my mind that what if we invest or buy some form of riskless or guaranteed instrument for the grace period. ?
Obviously the process is not that simple, going to a nearby ATM and withdrawing from your credit card would be the craziest thing that you can do, as it attracts ~20% interest from that moment and turns out to be very costly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Data Open; A Citadel Datathon at University of Waterloo</title>
      <link>/post/new/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/new/</guid>
      <description>Data Open is a competition/hackathon that brings together the best minds in mathematics, engineering, STEM to collaborate and compete using the world&amp;rsquo;s most important data sets. Over 100 undergraduate and graduate students from University of Toronto, Waterloo are invited to participate after an initial 60 minute assesment test. Our team won the first place for our work Improving 311 service through Geospatial and Time Series Analysis
  Congratulations to Team 6 for winning The Data Open!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>